{
  "History": [
    {
      "question": "Britain and France declared war on Germany on 3 September 1939 after the German invasion of which country?Britain and France declared war on Germany on 3 September 1939 after the German invasion of which country?",
      "options": [
        "Denmark",
        "Poland",
        "Czechoslovakia",
        "India"
      ],
      "correct": "Poland",
      "id": "H1",
      "givenAns": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "When did Germany invade the USSR?",
      "options": [
        "April 1940",
        "May 1940",
        "June 1941",
        "Jan 1939"
      ],
      "correct": "June 1941",
      "id": "H2",
      "givenAns": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the name of Britain's new bombing policy in May 1942 that targeted German cities?",
      "options": [
        "Tactical bombing",
        "Area bombing",
        "Precision bombing",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "correct": "Area bombing",
      "id": "H3",
      "givenAns": ""
    }
  ],
  "Maths": [
    {
      "question": "2+3+7 = ?",
      "options": [
        "15",
        "13",
        "12",
        "11"
      ],
      "correct": "12",
      "id": "H1",
      "givenAns": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "5+(10/2)-9 = ?",
      "options": [
        "-1",
        "0",
        "1",
        "2"
      ],
      "correct": "1",
      "id": "H2",
      "givenAns": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "5*5+5*5 = ?",
      "options": [
        "150",
        "250",
        "100",
        "50"
      ],
      "correct": "50",
      "id": "H3",
      "givenAns": ""
    }
  ],
  "Physics": [
    {
      "question": "The speed of light will be minimum while passing through_______",
      "options": [
        "Water",
        "Vaccum",
        "Air",
        "Glass"
      ],
      "correct": "Glass",
      "id": "H1",
      "givenAns": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a vector quantity?",
      "options": [
        "Speed",
        "Velocity",
        "Torque",
        "Displacement"
      ],
      "correct": "Speed",
      "id": "H2",
      "givenAns": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "The most suitable unit for expressing nuclear radius is_______",
      "options": [
        "Micro",
        "Nano",
        "Fermi",
        "Angstrom"
      ],
      "correct": "Fermi",
      "id": "H3",
      "givenAns": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "Rain drops acquire spherical shape due to _______",
      "options": [
        "Viscosity",
        "Surface Tension",
        "Friction",
        "Elasticity"
      ],
      "correct": "Surface Tension",
      "id": "H4",
      "givenAns": ""
    }
  ],
  "Chemistry": [
    {
      "question": "What is the structure of IF7 ?",
      "options": [
        "Triagonal bipyramid",
        "Pentagonal bipyramid",
        "tetrahedral",
        "Square pyramid"
      ],
      "correct": "Pentagonal bipyramid",
      "id": "H1",
      "givenAns": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "Which pair of atoms has the highest electronegativity difference?",
      "options": [
        "F-F",
        "Ca-F",
        "H-F",
        "Na-F"
      ],
      "correct": "Na-F",
      "id": "H2",
      "givenAns": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "Among the given nutrients, milk is a poor source of",
      "options": [
        "Calcium",
        "Protein",
        "Vitamin C",
        "Carbohydrate"
      ],
      "correct": "Vitamin C",
      "id": "H3",
      "givenAns": ""
    }
  ],
  "English": [
    {
      "question": "The thief was sent to _____ prison",
      "options": [
        "a",
        "an",
        "the",
        "no article"
      ],
      "correct": "the",
      "id": "H1",
      "givenAns": ""
    }
  ],
  "temp": [
    {
      "question": "",
      "options": [
        "",
        "",
        "",
        ""
      ],
      "correct": "",
      "id": "H",
      "givenAns": ""
    }
  ]
}